headline	details
"Stanford Offering Free Tuition To Students Whose Families Make Less Than $125,000"	"As part of an effort to make college accessible and affordable, Stanford University has announced that it will offer free tuition to students whose parents make less than $125,000 per year. "
Judge: Woman Can File Divorce Papers On Facebook	"According to a report in the New York Daily News, a judge in New York granted a woman the right to serve her husband divorce papers via a private Facebook message because he refuses to provide an address, ruling that “This transmittal shall be repeated by plaintiff’s attorney to defendant once a week for three consecutive weeks or until acknowledged.”"
Supporters Raise $840K For Anti–Gay Marriage Pizza Joint	"After the owners of an Indiana pizzeria said they wouldn’t be comfortable catering gay weddings, in a statement that prompted threats and led them to close their establishment, supporters started an online fundraiser for their family that has raised more than $840,000. "
Report: High School Students Using Instagram To Choose Colleges	"According to a report in Time magazine, many high school students are using Instagram to choose which college they will attend by checking out photos others have taken of the campus, at parties, or around town, which they say provide a more realistic look at the school than the materials the school publishes online. "
McDonald’s Raising Wages 10% To Attract Better Workers	"McDonald’s has announced that beginning July 1, it is raising employee wages at corporate-owned locations 10 percent, from an average of $9.01 per hour to an average of $9.90 per hour, which experts say will help it attract better and more sought-after employees. "
Madame Tussauds Appoints ‘Tissue Attendant’ To Comfort One Direction Fans	"A spokesman for Madame Tussauds wax museum in London said in a statement that museum officials brought in 150 boxes of tissues to the One Direction exhibit and appointed a “tissue attendant” to help fans grieving over the departure of Zayn Malik, whose wax figure will not be removed from the lineup. "
Karl Lagerfeld’s Cat Made $3 Million Last Year From Modeling Gigs	"In an interview with New York magazine, fashion designer Karl Lagerfeld said that his cat, Choupette, made $3 million from two modeling gigs last year, one for a German car ad and the other for a Japanese beauty product. "
Study: Kids Allowed To Sip Alcohol Drink More As Teens	"According to a new study, kids who have sipped alcohol by the sixth grade are five times more likely to have had a full drink by high school and four times more likely to get drunk or binge drink as teens."
NBC Announces Next Live Musical Will Be ‘The Wiz’	"NBC has announced its next live holiday musical production will be The Wiz, a long-running musical theater version of The Wizard Of Oz starring a predominantly African-American cast, which was turned into a movie starring Michael Jackson in 1978. "
Study: Amount Of Time Spent With Kids Doesn’t Matter	"A new study has found that the amount of time parents spend with kids between ages 3 and 11 has less correlation with how they turn out than the quality of their time spent together, so it’s important that parents aren’t too stressed, anxious, or sleep-deprived when they’re interacting with their kids. "
McDonald’s Debuts Big Mac Clothing Line	"McDonald’s debuted a new lifestyle product line featuring clothes printed with patterns of Big Mac burgers as part of its “imlovinit24” corporate marketing campaign, which involved staging 24 McDonald’s-themed stunts over 24 hours. "
Parents Let Kids Play On Vietnam War Memorial	"Parents visiting Washington, D.C. with their kids this week sparked outrage and controversy by encouraging them to climb and play on the Vietnam Women’s Memorial, which honors U.S. women who served in Vietnam. "
New Facebook ‘On This Day’ Feature Unearths Photos From Past	"Facebook has introduced a new feature called On This Day that allows users to unearth photos they shared or were tagged in from the past, which they can then choose to share with friends. "
Catholic High School Insists On Pre-Approving Prom Dresses	"According to a report in the York Daily Record, a Catholic high school in McSherrystown, PA has instituted a new policy requiring female students to submit photos of their intended prom dresses to school faculty for pre-approval before they can buy tickets to prom. "
Gap CEO Hints At Vending Machines For Clothes	"In an interview with Fast Company, Gap CEO Art Peck said that as part of his company’s push to incorporate technology into its operations, he has thought about the possibility of introducing vending machines for clothes. "